{
    "id": "3ff2b45c872543e38290d3cf60c854e1",
    "title": "Collective nouns exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "33e19ecd12cb45a885c5f2b8fb4fff97",
            "title": "Collective Nouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Our audience …………….. always been the affluent urban elite.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The audience at the open-air stadium ………………… not as large as had been expected.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The audience …………………. enthralled by her performance.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Audiences throughout the world ……………….. been captivated by Chaplin’s films.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The public ………………….. stringent laws to deal with terrorists.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "want",
                        "wants"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The public …………….. not satisfied with the relief measures taken during the floods.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The team ………………… practising at the stadium.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The team ………………. for Australia tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is leaving",
                        "are leaving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A family with four children ………………. next door.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "live",
                        "lives"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My family …………………. going to be there.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}